(Howard:)Yeah. A grown man moving
into his own apartment.
Crazy times. See ya!
(Bernadette:)Ignore him.
He's just using humor
to express how...
(Bernadette:)happy he is.
(Stuart:)It's okay. I know he loves me.
(Bernadette:)Sure he does.
(Bernadette:)Well, let us know
when you're all settled in.
(Stuart:)I will. And I really can't
thank you guys enough.
(engine starts)
Our pleasure.
(Amy:)Bye.
Bye.
WOLOWITZ:
He's gone!
Let's start in the garage!
(Raj:)Okay, so once we receive
the next image
(Raj:)and compare it to the ones
we've already collected,
(Raj:)we'll know what it is
that we found.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, perhaps it's a
Heliosheath scintillation.
(Raj:)It could be
a trans-Neptunian object.